<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Galilee Bedouin Camplodge - Accomodations</title><link href="https://galilee-bedouin-camplodge.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://galilee-bedouin-camplodge.com/feeds/accomodations.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://galilee-bedouin-camplodge.com/</id><updated>2012-07-15T13:34:00+02:00</updated><entry><title>Camping</title><link href="https://galilee-bedouin-camplodge.com/accomodations/camping.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2012-07-15T13:34:00+02:00</published><updated>2012-07-15T13:34:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Nagasaki45</name></author><id>tag:galilee-bedouin-camplodge.com,2012-07-15:/accomodations/camping.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Camp at our site with your own tent and enjoy the gardens Israeli coastal plains views.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;If you are on the budget, you are more then welcome to camp at our place with your own tent.
The camping site is located in our garden with views to the Tzipori river and the sea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As campers you can enjoy all the facilities we offer: Cooking in the shared kitchen at the main tent and use our showers and toilets.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Accomodations"></category><category term="camping"></category><category term="nature"></category><category term="family tent"></category><category term="hiking"></category><category term="israel trail"></category></entry><entry><title>The White Khan</title><link href="https://galilee-bedouin-camplodge.com/accomodations/shared-room.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2012-07-15T13:33:00+02:00</published><updated>2012-07-15T13:33:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Nagasaki45</name></author><id>tag:galilee-bedouin-camplodge.com,2012-07-15:/accomodations/shared-room.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;10-bed shared dormitory on a suburban environment. Chill-out in the spirit of the Bedouin hospitality.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The White Khan is located at the center of our site. During the winter it is warmed with wood-burning stove, allowing our guests to enjoy the warm and cosy atmosphere even on the coldest days. At the summertime the Khan is open and calm wind from the wadi flows through its windows. It is also equipped with air conditioner. There is a fully equipped kitchen In the Khan for your use, including refrigerator, hob, stove, sink with hot water and cooking / serving utensils. The Khan floor is covered with mats, and there are many mattresses and pillows for your convenience. Outside is a spacious shaded chill-out area built in the spirit of the Bedouin hospitality, with views of the garden. There are also a  place for campfire and comfortable sitting areas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guests of the white Khan have free WiFi access and shared toilets and showers. Bed linen and towels are provided.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Accomodations"></category><category term="Dormitory"></category><category term="Shared room"></category><category term="khan"></category></entry><entry><title>Family studio</title><link href="https://galilee-bedouin-camplodge.com/accomodations/studio-room.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2012-07-15T13:33:00+02:00</published><updated>2012-07-15T13:33:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Izhar Gurion</name></author><id>tag:galilee-bedouin-camplodge.com,2012-07-15:/accomodations/studio-room.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Our studio is perfect for a family vacation and has a shady sitting area under the old olive tree.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is 3 bed room (2 double and 1 single) with private bathroom and a small kitchen (with refrigerator, electric plate for cooking and free coffee and tea).
The room is perfect for a family vacation and has a shady sitting area under the old olive tree. Free breakfast and Wi-Fi. Bed linen and towels are provided.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Accomodations"></category><category term="privet room"></category><category term="family vacation"></category><category term="studio"></category><category term="bathroom"></category></entry><entry><title>Private tipi tent</title><link href="https://galilee-bedouin-camplodge.com/accomodations/tipi-tent.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2012-07-15T13:33:00+02:00</published><updated>2012-07-15T13:33:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Izhar Gurion</name></author><id>tag:galilee-bedouin-camplodge.com,2012-07-15:/accomodations/tipi-tent.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Under the broad carob tree, the Tipi tent offer natural experience to couples or single travelers alike.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is a Tipi tent, snugged under a broad carob tree, shading in its foliage.
The top of the tent is opened in the summer time to keep the tent vented and cool.
It contains 1 small double bed and Coffee corner inside the tent. Shared bathroom and Wi-Fi. Bed linen and towels are provided.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Accomodations"></category><category term="tipi"></category><category term="tent"></category><category term="unique"></category><category term="vacation"></category></entry><entry><title>Private train wagon</title><link href="https://galilee-bedouin-camplodge.com/accomodations/train-wagon.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2012-07-15T13:33:00+02:00</published><updated>2012-07-15T13:33:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Izhar Gurion</name></author><id>tag:galilee-bedouin-camplodge.com,2012-07-15:/accomodations/train-wagon.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Unique privet room in a old British train wagon which was renovated by us. Shady retreat under the vines in the garden.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This room is set in an old British train wagon which was renovated by us in a way that preserves the original look, wood scents and texture.
It has a shady retreat under the vines in the garden.
It can accommodate up to 3 people. Has air conditioning, kitchenette and Shared bathroom.
Free breakfast, coffee and Wi-Fi. Bed linen and towels are provided.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Accomodations"></category><category term="privet room"></category><category term="train wagon"></category><category term="british"></category><category term="railwais"></category><category term="garden"></category><category term="vines"></category></entry></feed>